https://www.everlast.com/privacy-policy

Sign Up & Take
15% Off*
Your First Order On Everlast.com
Be the first to know about new products, special offers, and more.
JOIN
*Discount available for new subscribers only. Code will be emailed upon submission.
By submitting, you agree to these Terms & Conditions. You may unsubscribe at any time. View Contact Info and Privacy Policy.
Powered by Mageplaza
Menu
FightBoxingGlovesTraining GlovesFight GlovesProtective EquipmentMouthguardsProtective HeadgearGroin ProtectorsHand WrapsTraditional Hand WrapsEvergel Hand WrapsPunching BagsHeavy Bags & StandsFree Standing Heavy BagsSpecialty Heavy BagsSpeed Bags & PlatformsPunching Bag AccessoriesTraining EquipmentPunch MittsPunch & Strike ShieldsCorner SuppliesNovelty & Fan GearRings & AccessoriesMMAGlovesTraining & Sparring GlovesFight GlovesProtective EquipmentHand WrapsPunching BagsTraining EquipmentFitnessTrainingFight FitnessActivity Trackers & ScalesGym BagsYogaFashionMenTopsBottomsCompetition ApparelFootwearHatsWomenTopsBottomsCompetition ApparelFootwearHatsDealsSaleBundlesGlove FinderLong Live#TeamEverlast BlogPro TeamLogin / SignupLoginCreate Account
Account
Settings
Currency
USA
CANADA
EUR - Euro
Home
Privacy Policy
USD
PRIVACY POLICY
This Privacy Policy describes how Everlast Worldwide ("Everlast") collects, uses, shares and protects personal information from and about you. This Privacy Policy applies to Everlast's online services and applications, including but not limited to our website and mobile app. By using the Everlast website and/or mobile app, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to our methods of collection, use and sharing of information that is described herein. We may change, update or add to this Privacy Policy at any time, so we encourage you to review it periodically.
This Privacy Policy also describes options you have about how Everlast collects and uses your personal information. You may exercise these options at any time.
If you have any questions about this Everlast Privacy Policy, please contact us at ecommerce@everlast.com.
How We Collect Information
1. PROVIDED DIRECTLY BY YOU
When you use our website, Everlast may ask you to provide us with one or more of the following:
Your name
Your mailing address
Your e-mail address
Your phone number
Your credit/debit card number and expiration date
Your date of birth
Your gender
Your personal interests
If you choose not to provide the requested information, Everlast may not be able to provide you with services or information.
2. Automated Collection
Everlast may collect information about the device you use to access our website or mobile app, such as your computer's IP address, your browser type, your operating system and other technical information. Our mobile app may also collect information about your location, if enabled.
The everlast.com website uses cookies, web beacons, pixel tags or other tracking technologies to receive and store certain information, such as the pages you view, the features you use, the links you click, and when you open or click a link in a message from us. These tracking technologies will help you navigate the website and enhance or personalize your online shopping experience. They may be used to generate the ads you see on the everlast.com website and on other websites.
You can set your browser to not accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, which will give you the option to decide whether or not to accept a cookie.
Everlast may combine the information obtained through automated collection with personal information that you have provided to us directly, and use it as described in this Privacy Policy.
How We Use Information
Everlast may use the information that we collect from and about you for any or all of the following:
To send you information about products, sales and promotions (subject to your option to opt-out)
To enhance your shopping experience
To process and fill an order, return or exchange
To send you e-mails or text messages to confirm an order status
To learn more about your shopping preferences
To improve the effectiveness of our website and mobile app
To address problems with or improve our products and services
To conduct research on and analyze trends and statistics
To protect the security or integrity of the website and mobile app
To prevent fraud
To contact you
For legal purposes, such as to assist law enforcement or respond to legal inquiries
You always have the choice not to receive promotional e-mails from us, and you can opt out by contacting our customer service department at ecommerce@everlast.com or unsubscribe to e-mails via the opt out link included in each promotional e-mail. It may take up to 7 days to process your request, during which time you may continue to receive communications from us.
If you change your mind, you can start receiving e-mails from us again by changing your preferences in your online account or by contacting our customer service department at ecommerce@everlast.com.
Please note that when you make an online purchase from Everlast, we will confirm your order status and shipment of the products by e-mail, even if you have opted out of receiving promotional e-mails. We may also contact you by e-mail with questions regarding your order.
How We Share Information
Everlast may share the information that we collect from and about you for any or all of the following:
With companies that provide support services to Everlast, in order to manage customer information and perform services on behalf of Everlast, including but not limited to running promotions, filling orders, processing payments, sending communications to our customers and conducting surveys. Everlast prohibits all of these support service providers from making any further use or disclosure of your information for any other purpose.
With law enforcement or government authorities in order to comply with laws or regulations or in response to a valid subpoena, order or government request.
With law enforcement in order to protect the rights, property or safety of Everlast or others.
With legal personnel to enforce our Terms & Conditions and other agreements.
We may share aggregated anonymous data (information that does not identify a specific individual) with third parties for lawful purposes.
In the case of a sale or other transfer of some or all of our business, we may transfer the your information to the buyer or transferee as part of the transaction.
How We Protect Your Information
Everlast wants to provide you with a safe website experience. We maintain administrative, electronic and physical, safeguards to protect your personal information. When you provide us with personal information on the website or through the mobile app, we use industry standard methods to protect your information as it is transmitted to us. However, no Internet website or system is completely secure, and you are responsible for taking reasonable steps to protect your personal information.
Updating Your Information
You can access and update your personal information by logging into your account and editing your personal information in your account profile. In the alternative, you can contact our customer service department at ecommerce@everlast.com and request that changes be made. Please note that any such request to update your personal information may take up to 7 days.
Privacy of Children's Personal Information
Everlast is committed to protecting the privacy and safety of children in connection with online activities. We do not knowingly request or collect personally identifiable information online from anyone under the age of 13. Our website is a general audience site and is not targeted to or intended for use by children.
California Privacy Rights
Your Rights under the CCPA
Under this Privacy Policy, and by law if you are a resident of California, you have the following rights:
• The right to notice. you must be properly notified which categories of Personal Data are being collected and the purposes for which the Personal Data is being used.
• The right to access / the right to request. The CCPA permits you to request and obtain from the Company information regarding the disclosure of your Personal Data that has been collected in the past 12 months by the Company or its subsidiaries to a third-party for the third party's direct marketing purposes.
• The right to say no to the sale of Personal Data. You also have the right to ask the Company not to sell your Personal Data to third parties. You can submit such a request by visiting our "Do Not Sell My Personal Information" section or web page.
The right to know about your Personal Data. You have the right to request and obtain from the Company information regarding the disclosure of the following:
The categories of Personal Data collected
The sources from which the Personal Data was collected
The business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling the Personal Data
Categories of third parties with whom We share Personal Data
The specific pieces of Personal Data we collected about you
The right to delete Personal Data. You also have the right to request the deletion of your Personal Data that have been collected in the past 12 months.
The right not to be discriminated against. You have the right not to be discriminated against for exercising any of your Consumer's rights, including by:
Denying goods or services to you
Charging different prices or rates for goods or services, including the use of discounts or other benefits or imposing penalties
Providing a different level or quality of goods or services to you
Suggesting that you will receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.
Exercising your CCPA Data Protection Rights
In order to exercise any of your rights under the CCPA, as a California resident, you can fill out the Personal Data Request form or call us Toll Free at 800-821-7930.
Our dedicated Customer Service team will disclose and deliver the required information free of charge within 45 days of receiving your verifiable request. The time period to provide the required information may be extended once by an additional 45 days when reasonably necessary and with prior notice.
Do Not Sell My Personal Information
We do not sell personal information. However, the Service Providers we partner with (for example, our advertising partners) may use technology on the Service that "sells" personal information as defined by the CCPA law.
If you wish to opt out of the use of your personal information for interest-based advertising purposes and these potential sales as defined under CCPA law, you may do so by following the instructions below.
Please note that any opt out is specific to the browser you use. You may need to opt out on every browser that you use.
Website
You can opt out of receiving ads that are personalized as served by our Service Providers by following our instructions presented in our Privacy Policy under Information About Third-Party Cookies and Interest-Based Advertising.
Mobile Devices
Your mobile device may give you the ability to opt out of the use of information about the apps you use in order to serve you ads that are targeted to your interests:
"Opt out of Interest-Based Ads" or "Opt out of Ads Personalization" on Android devices
"Limit Ad Tracking" on iOS devices
You can also stop the collection of location information from your mobile device by changing the preferences on your mobile device.
Links to Third Party Websites
The everlast.com website may contain links to other sites, which may have privacy policies that differ from this one. We are not responsible for the content or practices of any linked third party website. You should always review the privacy policy of any site that you access through our website.
CONTACT US
For questions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us as follows:
Everlast Worldwide
Attn: Customer Service
1900 HWY DD
Moberly, MO 65270
Or you may contact us by phone at 800-821-7930, Monday-Friday, 8 am - 5 pm CST.
© 2020 Everlast Worldwide, Inc.
Customer ID :
© 2020 Everlast Worldwide, Inc.
Customer ID :
217-689-747
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use
